[
    {
        "id": "687f157a19665",
        "question": "Who was the first Sultan of Brunei?",
        "optionA": "Sultan Muhamad Shah",
        "optionB": "Sultan Omar Ali Saifuddin",
        "optionC": "Sultan Sharif Ali",
        "optionD": "Sultan Ahmad",
        "correctAnswer": "A",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 04:37:14"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f166818ff1",
        "question": "In what century did Brunei first convert to Islam?",
        "optionA": "14th",
        "optionB": "19th",
        "optionC": "18th",
        "optionD": "15th",
        "correctAnswer": "A",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 04:41:12"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f183db5459",
        "question": "When was Brunei occupied by the Japanese during World War II?",
        "optionA": "World War II from December 16 1941 to June 10 1945",
        "optionB": "World War II from Novenber 16 1942 to April 21 1945",
        "optionC": "World War ll from December 21 1969 to May 1945",
        "optionD": "World War ll from September 11 1939 to June 21 1945",
        "correctAnswer": "A",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "HARD",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 04:49:01"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f18de927e6",
        "question": "In____________ Brunei was in the Protectarate State?",
        "optionA": "1880",
        "optionB": "1888",
        "optionC": "1543",
        "optionD": "1534",
        "correctAnswer": "B",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 04:51:42"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f19c0676ac",
        "question": "Identify one of the Brook's family member.",
        "optionA": "George Washington",
        "optionB": "Ferdinand Megallen",
        "optionC": "James Brooke",
        "optionD": "Donald Duck",
        "correctAnswer": "C",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 04:55:28"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f1a0e96ba5",
        "question": "In what century did Brunei first convert to Islam?",
        "optionA": "15th",
        "optionB": "17th",
        "optionC": "16th",
        "optionD": "14th",
        "correctAnswer": "D",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 04:56:46"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f1ac2c9527",
        "question": "What is the official language of Brunei?",
        "optionA": "Spanish",
        "optionB": "Malay",
        "optionC": "English",
        "optionD": "Chinese",
        "correctAnswer": "B",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 04:59:46"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f1b11e8e0c",
        "question": "What is the capital city of Brunei?",
        "optionA": "Bandar Seri Begawan",
        "optionB": "Labuan",
        "optionC": "European",
        "optionD": "China",
        "correctAnswer": "A",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 05:01:05"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f1c29556ab",
        "question": "When was oil discovered?",
        "optionA": "20th",
        "optionB": "12th",
        "optionC": "19th",
        "optionD": "13th",
        "correctAnswer": "A",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 05:05:45"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f1d0a03b8d",
        "question": "Who is the current Sultan of Brunei?",
        "optionA": "Sultan Sharif Ali",
        "optionB": "Sultan Hassanal Bolkiah",
        "optionC": "Sultan Omar Ali Saifuddin",
        "optionD": "Sultan Ahmad",
        "correctAnswer": "B",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 05:09:30"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f1e3663fa8",
        "question": "Which religion is most practiced in Brunei?",
        "optionA": "Islam",
        "optionB": "Chinese",
        "optionC": "Spanish",
        "optionD": "English",
        "correctAnswer": "A",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 05:14:30"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f1ecac3095",
        "question": "What is Brunei\u2019s official currency?",
        "optionA": "Ringgit",
        "optionB": "Dollar",
        "optionC": "Rupee",
        "optionD": "Yen",
        "correctAnswer": "B",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 05:16:58"
    },
    {
        "id": "687f1f5a1e617",
        "question": "When did Brunei become an independent country?",
        "optionA": "January 1 1984",
        "optionB": "May 4 1999",
        "optionC": "September 11 1935",
        "optionD": "October 15 1947",
        "correctAnswer": "A",
        "explanation": "",
        "subject": "BRUNEI_HISTORY",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "createdAt": "2025-07-22 05:19:22"
    }
]